[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Do you want them to take it better?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "them", "to", "take", "it", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "No, I didn't want them to take it badly in the first place.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "them", "to", "take", "it", "badly", "in", "the", "first", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Too easy, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Too", "easy", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I mean --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "That's what they call a home run, you know?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "they", "call", "a", "home", "run", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Do you have a moral code yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "moral", "code", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Of course I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What's your litmus test?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "litmus", "test", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, you can't.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "But what are we meant to do?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "are", "we", "meant", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "For a very long time, you would never have imagined being in Hollywood.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "a", "very", "long", "time", ",", "you", "would", "never", "have", "imagined", "being", "in", "Hollywood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "What is the reality of Hollywood excess?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "reality", "of", "Hollywood", "excess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Is it to not be famous too early?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "to", "not", "be", "famous", "too", "early", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Is it a lot easier, is my point, to be older and become famous?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "lot", "easier", ",", "is", "my", "point", ",", "to", "be", "older", "and", "become", "famous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"], "LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "It's the I can't believe my luck that I get up in the morning, have an idea, and I can start writing that idea and it will get made at the moment, you know?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "my", "luck", "that", "I", "get", "up", "in", "the", "morning", ",", "have", "an", "idea", ",", "and", "I", "can", "start", "writing", "that", "idea", "and", "it", "will", "get", "made", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "What I can't believe is the way you look, because we all fell in love back in Britain with fat, chubby Ricky.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "is", "the", "way", "you", "look", ",", "because", "we", "all", "fell", "in", "love", "back", "in", "Britain", "with", "fat", ",", "chubby", "Ricky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "tell", "me", "then", ",", "though", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "weight", "have", "you", "lost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Not much at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "much", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Hollywood smiley?", "question_tokens": ["Hollywood", "smiley", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "some", "free", "--", "those", "things", "in", "a", "luxury", "lounge", "once", ",", "those", "--", "I", "thought", "those", "made", "me", "gag", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "go", "on", "this", "vanity", "kick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "n't", "a", "vanity", "kick", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "``", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "would", "you", "be", "without", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "``", "The", "death", "of", "a", "fight-useless", "chubby", "loser", "with", "--", "who", "never", "cleans", "his", "teeth", "and", "stinks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Do you get more groupies now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "more", "groupies", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I don't -- never got groupies.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "never", "got", "groupies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 265, "question": "A svelte comedic auteur or as a chubby loser?", "question_tokens": ["A", "svelte", "comedic", "auteur", "or", "as", "a", "chubby", "loser", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I think --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "History of television?", "question_tokens": ["History", "of", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "\"Seinfeld,\" lovely show.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Seinfeld", ",", "''", "lovely", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "You love Twitter, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "love", "Twitter", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Why do you like it so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "like", "it", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I like it for lots of reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "it", "for", "lots", "of", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What were you getting at?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "getting", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, you know, as a comedian --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "as", "a", "comedian", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", ":"], "qSentId": 362, "question": "-- you'd fit in well looking like that?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "'d", "fit", "in", "well", "looking", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, I thought I looked intellectual there --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "I", "looked", "intellectual", "there", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Always?", "question_tokens": ["Always", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "How does your -- how does your atheism, which you're passionate about -- how does that play with your American audience, given that so many people in America are God-fearing people, and probably take exception to it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "your", "--", "how", "does", "your", "atheism", ",", "which", "you", "'re", "passionate", "about", "--", "how", "does", "that", "play", "with", "your", "American", "audience", ",", "given", "that", "so", "many", "people", "in", "America", "are", "God-fearing", "people", ",", "and", "probably", "take", "exception", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, but they shouldn't.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "but", "they", "should", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Do I do that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Should we play you what Steve Carell said about you?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "we", "play", "you", "what", "Steve", "Carell", "said", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Yes, please.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "please", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "do", "what", "Ricky", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Oh, not in a million years, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "not", "in", "a", "million", "years", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "would", "just", "get", "too", "skittish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 492, "question": "But you could play a Ricky Gervais character?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "could", "play", "a", "Ricky", "Gervais", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Perhaps, but to actually go in front of people and --", "answer_tokens": ["Perhaps", ",", "but", "to", "actually", "go", "in", "front", "of", "people", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "-- you're all heart, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "'re", "all", "heart", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Do you like Steve Carell?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "Steve", "Carell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "He's great.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What, with -- romantic love?", "question_tokens": ["What", ",", "with", "--", "romantic", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "IN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I'm assuming women.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "assuming", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Once?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Once.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Why haven't you married her yet?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "n't", "you", "married", "her", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, we are, really.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "are", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "ever", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Oh, I'd never say never.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'d", "never", "say", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "How do you show your romantic side?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "show", "your", "romantic", "side", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "It would be professional, really -- a moment in your life, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "professional", ",", "really", "--", "a", "moment", "in", "your", "life", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "There's loads of things whizzing through my head, but they're all from childhood.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "loads", "of", "things", "whizzing", "through", "my", "head", ",", "but", "they", "'re", "all", "from", "childhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "I just remembered one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "remembered", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Steve, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Steve", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Steve.", "answer_tokens": ["Steve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "You appeared how many times on Johnny Carson?", "question_tokens": ["You", "appeared", "how", "many", "times", "on", "Johnny", "Carson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "About 140 times.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "140", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Carson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "That has to be a record, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "has", "to", "be", "a", "record", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "Yes, Bob Hope was the most, and I was the second most.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Bob", "Hope", "was", "the", "most", ",", "and", "I", "was", "the", "second", "most", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Carousel"], "PERSON": ["Charlie Hartsock", "Vance DeGeneres"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", ":", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "What was the idea?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Well, Charlie Hartsock and Vance DeGeneres, who are my partners at Carousel, had this idea to kind of trace the -- trace comedy in terms of generations and -- and how it cross-pollinates and sort of look to people's inspirations.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Charlie", "Hartsock", "and", "Vance", "DeGeneres", ",", "who", "are", "my", "partners", "at", "Carousel", ",", "had", "this", "idea", "to", "kind", "of", "trace", "the", "--", "trace", "comedy", "in", "terms", "of", "generations", "and", "--", "and", "how", "it", "cross-pollinates", "and", "sort", "of", "look", "to", "people", "'s", "inspirations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "-- of superstar comedians, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "of", "superstar", "comedians", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 698, "question": "How are you -- how are you billing it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "--", "how", "are", "you", "billing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Well, I -- I don't know if it's a definitive history of comedy, but it is --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "it", "'s", "a", "definitive", "history", "of", "comedy", ",", "but", "it", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "On what makes people laugh?", "question_tokens": ["On", "what", "makes", "people", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "It's unique in the way in which the comedians talk about what they do.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "unique", "in", "the", "way", "in", "which", "the", "comedians", "talk", "about", "what", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "That happened between you and him?", "question_tokens": ["That", "happened", "between", "you", "and", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "That never happened.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "never", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Is there a stat -- when you all get together?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "stat", "--", "when", "you", "all", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "It's so subjective.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "so", "subjective", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "But biggest comedian wasn't your great burning ambition as a kid, was it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "biggest", "comedian", "was", "n't", "your", "great", "burning", "ambition", "as", "a", "kid", ",", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJS", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "And if it's funny, then, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "it", "'s", "funny", ",", "then", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "Let's talk a little break, gents.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "talk", "a", "little", "break", ",", "gents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "But you do -- do you thank God every day that these things happen?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "do", "--", "do", "you", "thank", "God", "every", "day", "that", "these", "things", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "It's a little bit like that, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "little", "bit", "like", "that", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "There -- there is no Moe and Larry here.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "--", "there", "is", "no", "Moe", "and", "Larry", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 874, "question": "It will hide your own lack of character, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "will", "hide", "your", "own", "lack", "of", "character", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 875, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Arkin"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 879, "question": "Who -- if I could trap you both on a desert island separately and you could have one comedian with you to make you laugh for the rest of your days, who would you take?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "--", "if", "I", "could", "trap", "you", "both", "on", "a", "desert", "island", "separately", "and", "you", "could", "have", "one", "comedian", "with", "you", "to", "make", "you", "laugh", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "days", ",", "who", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 880, "answer": "I would take Alan Arkin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "take", "Alan", "Arkin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "Because he makes -- one-to-one, he makes me laugh more than anyone I've ever met.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "makes", "--", "one-to-one", ",", "he", "makes", "me", "laugh", "more", "than", "anyone", "I", "'ve", "ever", "met", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 883, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 884, "answer": "He is -- he's so dry and so acerbic, he just -- I love being around the man.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "--", "he", "'s", "so", "dry", "and", "so", "acerbic", ",", "he", "just", "--", "I", "love", "being", "around", "the", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Who would you take?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "I'd probably take Groucho.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "probably", "take", "Groucho", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "If you're honest, did you prefer life before, when you were more anonymous, or have you actually embraced the whole fame thing with great enthusiasm?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "honest", ",", "did", "you", "prefer", "life", "before", ",", "when", "you", "were", "more", "anonymous", ",", "or", "have", "you", "actually", "embraced", "the", "whole", "fame", "thing", "with", "great", "enthusiasm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "It's much, much better to be rich and famous.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "much", ",", "much", "better", "to", "be", "rich", "and", "famous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "I like to think it might have been, but you never know, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "like", "to", "think", "it", "might", "have", "been", ",", "but", "you", "never", "know", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "It's a lot tougher to deal with, I think, if you get that kind of thing when you're younger.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "lot", "tougher", "to", "deal", "with", ",", "I", "think", ",", "if", "you", "get", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "when", "you", "'re", "younger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 965, "question": "Do you miss the character?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "miss", "the", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 966, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "do", "what", "Ricky", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "Oh, not in a million years.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "not", "in", "a", "million", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 972, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 973, "answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "would", "just", "get", "too", "skittish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 990, "question": "You've got seven movies on the go, is that right, over the next two years?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "seven", "movies", "on", "the", "go", ",", "is", "that", "right", ",", "over", "the", "next", "two", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 991, "answer": "And I'm writing a symphony and I have a cooking show coming up.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "'m", "writing", "a", "symphony", "and", "I", "have", "a", "cooking", "show", "coming", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 993, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 994, "answer": "Did you ever imagine here you'd be in Hollywood in your smart power suit, in the middle of a seven movie extravaganza --", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "here", "you", "'d", "be", "in", "Hollywood", "in", "your", "smart", "power", "suit", ",", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "seven", "movie", "extravaganza", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 996, "question": "-- earning you, potentially, a billion dollars?", "question_tokens": ["--", "earning", "you", ",", "potentially", ",", "a", "billion", "dollars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 997, "answer": "A billion dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "billion", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1001, "question": "You must pinch yourself a bit, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "pinch", "yourself", "a", "bit", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1002, "answer": "I'm always pinching myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "always", "pinching", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1027, "question": "You need to have had cigarettes burned on you for years, don't you, to be genuinely -- to make an audience laugh?", "question_tokens": ["You", "need", "to", "have", "had", "cigarettes", "burned", "on", "you", "for", "years", ",", "do", "n't", "you", ",", "to", "be", "genuinely", "--", "to", "make", "an", "audience", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", ":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1028, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]